Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel PAP. Today we are going to
discuss about ICICI Lombard.
Today the company has and clearly market
research channel has seen a decline of four percent, so
in the coming time we
can and should be discussed. If you
subscribe, you will see that
you see continuous
profit but it is not that good,
you have seen a
decline in profit.
Share it,
subscribe to the channel.
This
channel shows government's 11.50% share holding pattern.
If the promoters had
more than fifty percent, it would have been a good
thing, but right now you see the
interest of institutions is also quite good and the
promoters also have eight percent stake.
Here we will talk about ownership.
It was seen
decreasing a bit in the subscribe. Do
not subscribe, but when the
school is not visible, then the
appointed
here could not even lose much,
but still there is no one in the
square, we clearly know
that a decline was seen in the 1600 level stocks.
We saw it coming down to 1102 and
recovery from there. We were
going up to 13 but we are seeing a decline again.
Now we will see that a
double top is forming here. A
decline has been seen taking resistance around 1102
and it seems to be trying to break it. It
cannot be said that the decision was broken here but it has been
seen going below it
and the volume
can be subscribed on the designated channel from where
our resistance around 1111 becomes the
level around 1300. Let's
move on to the weekly chart. The support that we see on the weekly chart is
not as important as this
support. Here, 3
developed reds and from there you saw it jumping,
so this level is
approximately the 11th level.
Our resistance level appears to be 13. Let's
move on to the monthly chart. You will be able to see it on the monthly chart. The
support that you see on the monthly chart is
11:00. You will see this getting confirmed here as well.
Talking about resistance, 1301 is a
strong resistance, which is
also visible on the monthly chart. Here too,
you can see this level getting confirmed.
This was a system, after breakfast, a
good momentum was seen, so
in such a situation, the stock should be traded. So,
currently, the important resistance here is
Tera Toilet, another important level,
that is Rasuka Levels, which is very important for trading
because
after forming a base here, the stock gained momentum and was seen
trying to quote on this base again.
Once it broke it and went back up, then
if it breaks the 12th level again, then
you can see something special here.
You can
see the stock scanning on the downside and there
is a possibility that it can break 1100 and
try to go even lower. So,
if we want to think about buying here, then we have to do it
above 13
because you can also see the trend line here. If the
Tera 100 level is broken, then  This will be a
good thing for us.
I would like to explain to you on the weekly chart. You see, here
you saw a big green candle,
this means strong momentum was seen.
Now this decline has happened. It has been declining here for two weeks.
If it goes to 1267 tanker
or you see it returning from 1180, 1190 and
going above 1300. What does it
mean? The
trend that was going on here for so long, continuously,
you see people and people buying every day,
it is higher here and will
convert into higher low. On the weekly chart,
we can make a good buy here.
But if this does not happen, if the stock
goes below 12, then
we can be seen sustaining here again for the downside.
And if the level of 12 is broken, it
means this is not a small level, it is a very
important level. Below this, there will be a four
percent structure in it,
so we have to avoid buying there.
Whatever you want to buy here, for your show.  We have to
buy above here, if
we buy above 13 then you will
get good arrest recovery and here
your target will be the position rate, hence it
depends on the subscription, so this festival should be done, one should
not be hasty, there
is a company but there is no one in it, hence
above this we can think about buying here for short term or long term,
you like the video, Ghr
Cheating